allcontact.com 2012-01-05

# allContact: Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY** **  
(Last Revised: 28-NOV-2011)**

Thank you for visiting this web site. We understand the importance that Internet users place on privacy, and this Privacy Policy describes how we use personal information that is collected at this web site. Please read this Privacy Policy before using this site or submitting any personal information. By using this web site, you accept the privacy practices contained in this Privacy Policy. These privacy practices may change from time to time, but any changes will be posted. You are encouraged to review the Privacy Policy whenever you visit the web site to make sure you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.  
**Information We Collect**  
In order to serve our customers, we collect personally identifiable information, like names, addresses, phone numbers, email addresses, and sometimes credit card information when such information is voluntarily submitted by our visitors. We may use your personal information, transfer your personal information, and/or sell your personal information for any legal purpose, including, without limitation: (1) to deliver the products and/or services to you that you have requested; (2) to validate your compliance with the terms and conditions; (3) for content improvement and feedback purposes; (4) to reach you, when necessary, regarding your use of the web site or product(s); and (5) to bring retail opportunities and promotional offers to you by email, direct mail, telemarketing, and/or online banner advertising. When your information is provided to third parties, these third parties may include providers of direct marketing services and applications. We or these third parties may supplement the information we collect online with outside records to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you, and/or to offer you targeted advertising and other opportunities to purchase products and services that we believe may be of interest to you.  
We will NEVER share your credit card information with third parties unless you have given us explicit permission to do so, such as in order to fulfill a third party offer that you have accepted from us. By permitting us to collect this information, you will be able to receive free information on products and services that may be of interest to you. You also enable us to personalize your experience with us so that we can provide you with the highest quality of service. By submitting your email address on this web site, you agree to receive email from us and our third party advertisers. We, and our third party advertisers, may maintain separate email lists for different purposes. You can cancel your participation in any of these email lists at any time by clicking the opt-out link or other unsubscribe option that is included in the respective email. We only send emails to people who have authorized us to contact them, either directly, or through a third party. We do not send unsolicited commercial emails, because we hate spam as much as you do.  
In addition, you agree that by submitting your email address on this web site and/or registering to receive the product and/or service offered herein, such act constitutes a purchase, an inquiry, and/or an application for the purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (ATSR), 16 CFR ‘310 et seq. and any applicable state and local “do not call” regulations. We and our third party advertisers retain the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the ATSR and the applicable state regulations. 

**Third Party Actions  
**We do not control and are not liable for the actions of our third party marketers or advertisers. We pride ourselves in working with quality companies, but have no control over the actions of those third parties. While we are not liable for any of the actions of those third parties, you should feel free to give us feedback from time to time on your experiences with any third parties to whom we work with so that we may enhance our future service to all customers.  
**Cookies**  
We may use cookies to deliver content that is specific to your interests. Cookies are text files that are used by your computer’s web browser to store your preferences, and enable us to enhance your user experience with our web site.   
**IP Addresses  
**We may use your IP address to help prevent fraud, to help diagnose problems with our server, to gather broad demographic information, and to offer you products and services.  
**Third Party Web Sites**  
This web site and/or the products and/or services offered herein may direct you to web sites that are owned and/or controlled by third parties. We have no control over those third parties and are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices of those sites or companies.  
**Commitment to Data Security**  
All information collected from you is stored in a technically and physically secure environment. We use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, and we do everything we can to protect user information offline. Unfortunately, no transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we take reasonable measures to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of the information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.  
**Spam**  
If we determine that you are using allContact to elicit spam email, or we believe you do not in compliance with the CanSpamAct2003, we reserve the right to immediately terminate your account.  
We may also pursue legal action against you to cover any costs incurred in relation to the disruption of service the spam may have impacted on allContact.  
We investigate all spam incidents thoroughly before making any final decisions. If you believe you have received spam from an allContact user, please forward the email you received to us at staff@allcontact.com.  
**Contacting Us**  
If you need to contact us, you can email us at staff@allcontact.com.

We strive to provide excellent products, along with equally excellent customer service. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our practices, please feel free to contact us using one of the methods listed above.
